Open the bin
Pick up the bag
Tie the bag
Tie the bag again
Pick up bag
Put bag down
Close drawer
Open drawer
Pick up bag
A new bag
Stretch the new bag
Open the new bag
Put bag into the bin
Stretch bag
Close the trash bin
put gloves on both hands
pick up sponge
open the tap
move things
put liquid
pick up knife
wash knife
pick up spoon
wash spoon
open tap
rinse spoon
put spoon down
rinse knife
put knife down
close tap
pick up mug
wash mug
open tap
rinse mug
close tap
put mug
pick up mug
wash mug
open tap
rinse mug
close tap
put mug
pick up glass
wash glass
open tap
rinse glass
close tap
put glass into drainer
pick up plate
wash plate
open tap
rinse plate
close tap
put plate into drainer
pick up mug
wash mug
open tap
rinse mug
close tap
put mug into drainer
pick up mug
pick up glass
wash glass
open tap
rinse glass
close tap
put glass into drainer
pick up plate from the left
wash plate
open tap
rinse plate
close top
put plate into drainer
empty the sink
remove gloves
pick up water filter
open tap while holding the water filter
fill water filter
close tap
carry water filter
put water filter down
[END SUBTITLE]